[{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678805999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":26,"rt":10499,"timeElapsed":33585},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678815167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":9167,"timeElapsed":42753},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678818167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2999,"timeElapsed":45753},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678822801,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":4634,"timeElapsed":50387},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678827850,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":5048,"timeElapsed":55436},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678829915,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":2064,"timeElapsed":57501},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678833134,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":3218,"timeElapsed":60720},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678837770,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":4635,"timeElapsed":65356},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678842811,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"239","question":"Do you have anything planned in the coming weeks or months for which you are especially excited? If so, describe this plan. If not, describe something you would like to plan for the coming weeks or months if you had the time or resources.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":5041,"timeElapsed":70397},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678851923,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":8144,"timeElapsed":79509},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678855582,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3658,"timeElapsed":83168},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735678860438,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":4855,"timeElapsed":88024},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679156405,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":295966,"timeElapsed":383991},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679159122,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":2716,"timeElapsed":386708},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679160776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":27,"rt":1653,"timeElapsed":388362},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679162339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1563,"timeElapsed":389925},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168290,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":49,"rt":5950,"timeElapsed":395876},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679171363,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3073,"timeElapsed":398949},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679230584,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":58377,"timeElapsed":458170},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679244855,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":14270,"timeElapsed":472441},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679246473,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":1618,"timeElapsed":474059},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679247782,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1308,"timeElapsed":475368},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679249404,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":1620,"timeElapsed":476990},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679250685,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":1281,"timeElapsed":478271},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679252131,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":1445,"timeElapsed":479717},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679253992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1861,"timeElapsed":481578},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679255592,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"100","question":"If you died today, what would be your biggest regret?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":1599,"timeElapsed":483178},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679401665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":145049,"timeElapsed":629251},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679402579,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":914,"timeElapsed":630165},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679405914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":43,"rt":3334,"timeElapsed":633500},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679406920,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":48,"rt":1005,"timeElapsed":634506},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679409308,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":2388,"timeElapsed":636894},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679411097,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":22,"rt":1788,"timeElapsed":638683},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679412842,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":1745,"timeElapsed":640428},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679414688,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":1846,"timeElapsed":642274},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679416951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"80","question":"If you could send one cultural object to aliens to try to convince them of the worth of humanity, what would it be?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2262,"timeElapsed":644537},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430870,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":12938,"timeElapsed":658456},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679434439,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":3568,"timeElapsed":662025},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679435744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1304,"timeElapsed":663330},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679439155,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3410,"timeElapsed":666741},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679442067,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":2912,"timeElapsed":669653},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679444250,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2181,"timeElapsed":671836},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679445392,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":62,"rt":1142,"timeElapsed":672978},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679446657,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1264,"timeElapsed":674243},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679448155,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1498,"timeElapsed":675741},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679449757,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"142","question":"Describe a current pet or previous pet you have had.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1602,"timeElapsed":677343},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679591364,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":140495,"timeElapsed":818949},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679592633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1269,"timeElapsed":820219},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679593589,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":955,"timeElapsed":821175},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679594751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1161,"timeElapsed":822337},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679596877,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":2126,"timeElapsed":824463},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679598220,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":1342,"timeElapsed":825806},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679600398,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":80,"rt":2177,"timeElapsed":827984},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679602021,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":1623,"timeElapsed":829607},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679603256,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"32","question":"Of all the people in your family, whose death would you find most tragic or difficult? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":1235,"timeElapsed":830842},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679607765,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":3650,"timeElapsed":835351},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679609749,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":1984,"timeElapsed":837335},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679610791,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":1042,"timeElapsed":838377},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679613639,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2847,"timeElapsed":841225},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679619407,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":5768,"timeElapsed":846993},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679621497,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":21,"rt":2089,"timeElapsed":849083},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679623099,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":1601,"timeElapsed":850685},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679719262,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":96162,"timeElapsed":946848},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679721119,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"163","question":"Did you have a class pet when you were in elementary school? Do you remember the pet’s name? What kind of animal was it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":35,"rt":1857,"timeElapsed":948705},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679724840,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":2969,"timeElapsed":952426},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679726196,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":1356,"timeElapsed":953782},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679730838,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":4641,"timeElapsed":958424},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679731977,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":50,"rt":1139,"timeElapsed":959563},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679734070,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2092,"timeElapsed":961656},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679735499,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":1428,"timeElapsed":963085},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679736825,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":1325,"timeElapsed":964411},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679738744,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1919,"timeElapsed":966330},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679739951,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"38","question":"Describe a person or idea that inspires you or gives you hope.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":1206,"timeElapsed":967537},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679769167,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":56,"rt":27168,"timeElapsed":996753},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679770467,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":1299,"timeElapsed":998053},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679774157,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":3689,"timeElapsed":1001743},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679776774,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":46,"rt":2616,"timeElapsed":1004360},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679779018,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":55,"rt":2244,"timeElapsed":1006604},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679780319,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":57,"rt":1300,"timeElapsed":1007905},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679783914,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":3595,"timeElapsed":1011500},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679787356,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":52,"rt":3442,"timeElapsed":1014942},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679790350,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":2994,"timeElapsed":1017936},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679792733,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"180","question":"What is your job or occupation? Describe a typical day.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":53,"rt":2382,"timeElapsed":1020319},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679796793,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":37,"rt":3343,"timeElapsed":1024379},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679798310,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1516,"timeElapsed":1025896},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679799625,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":1315,"timeElapsed":1027211},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679800999,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":30,"rt":1373,"timeElapsed":1028585},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679871423,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":31,"rt":70423,"timeElapsed":1099009},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679899829,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":25,"rt":28405,"timeElapsed":1127415},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679902016,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":20,"rt":2187,"timeElapsed":1129602},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679939572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":32,"rt":37555,"timeElapsed":1167158},{"subjectID":"8zc1v7cc2v","prolificID":"660cd7b61a24eeff3eac6e93","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b2b78a1f56fb7065b8d","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679942865,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"78","question":"What is your favorite organ of the body and why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":3292,"timeElapsed":1170450}]